Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Association of America Slide Library, 1891-2000 and undated RL.00965
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Presentations and Presentation Slides Series, 1960s-1980s and undated
  - Presentations: (Box PR1)
    - Common Sense (SLB0012) (Box PR3)
    - What?s New Under the Sun (SLB0013) (Box PR3)
    - Miss America ( IOA, [1975?]) (SLB0014) (Box PR3)
      This presentation features slides of a campaign that tested awareness. The industry used ads with Miss America's name (Shirley Cothran) and subsequent testing as proof of outdoor advertising effectiveness.
    - IOA Membership (IOA) (SLB0015) (Box PR3)
    - Inflation (IOA) (SLB0016) (Box PR3)
    - Target Group Index (SLB0017) (Box PR3)
    - Best Painted Bulletin Displays - Master General Foods and duplicates (IOA) (SLB0018) (Box PR3)
    - Cole Creative Presentation (SLB0019) (Box PR3)
    - Garrett Orr Presentation (SLB0020) (Box PR3)
    - Take a Look at Birmingham (SLB0021) (Box PR4)
    - Planning an Outdoor Program, Outdoor Seminar, Toronto, Ontario, 10/16/65 (SLB0022) (Box PR4)
    - Presentation to Food Market Institute, 3/25/78 (SLB0023) (Box PR4)
    - Outdoor for Passenger Cars (SLB0024) (Box PR4)
    - Wall-Dog Era and Story of Outdoor Advertising (scripts only) (SLB0025) (Box PR4)
    - Various Presentations (SLB0026 and SLB0027), 2 folders (Box PR4)
  - Miscellaneous presentation slides (Box PR5)
  - Miscellaneous presentation slides (Box PR6)
  - Miscellaneous presentation slides (Box PR7)
  - Miscellaneous presentation slides (Box PR8)
  - Miscellaneous presentation slides (Box PR9)
  - Miscellaneous presentation slides (Box PR10)
  - Miscellaneous presentation slides (Box PR11)
  - Glass Presentation Slides (Box PR12)
    These slides are encased in glass. Most appear to be a part of a presentation by Outdoor Advertising Incorporated including images of ads for 7-Up and Budweiser (Anheuser Busch). There is also a wide variety of street signs, spectaculars, and other signs.
  - Presentation Scripts on Audiocassette (master and use copies): (Box PR13)
    - Outdoor Goes to College (Box PR13)
    - It Pays to be Creative, F and K (IOA) (Box PR13)
    - Media Insurance, F and K (IOA) (Box PR13)
- Additions Run 1, 1960-2000 and undated; 1
  - Awards, 1986-2000; 1
    - Merit winners, 1999 (Box ADD1)
    - 1986 Obies (Box ADD1)
    - 1990 Obie finalists, 4 folders (Box ADD1)
    - 1994-1995 Obies, 5 folders (Box ADD1)
    - 1994-1995 Obies, 7 folders (Box ADD2)
    - 1995 Obies--Ballots (Box ADD2)
    - 1995 Obies--Entries (forms) (Box ADD2)
    - 1995 Obies--Entries (forms), 20 folders (Box ADD3)
    - 1995 Obies--Finalists (Box ADD4)
    - 1995 Obies--Winners, 3 folders (Box ADD4)
    - 1996 Obies--Entries--Campaign, 6 folders (Box ADD4)
    - 1996 Obies--Entries--Campaign, 6 folders (Box ADD5)
    - 1996 Obies--Entries--Single execution, 6 folders (Box ADD5)
    - 1996 Obies--Entries--Single execution, 11 folders (Box ADD6)
    - 1996 Obies--Entries--Sample entry forms (Box ADD6)
    - 1996 Obies--Finalists, 2 folders (Box ADD6)
    - 1996 Obies--Finalists, 3 folders (Box ADD7)
    - 1997 Obies--Entries--International Out-of-Home, 4 folders (Box ADD7)
    - 1997 Obies--Finalists, 2 folders (Box ADD7)
    - 1997 Obies--Miscellaneous slides (Box ADD7)
    - 1998 Obies--Entries--International Out-of-Home, 13 folders (Box ADD8)
    - 1998 Obies--Finalists, 4 folders (Box ADD9)
    - 1998 Obies--Hall of Fame (Levi's) (Box ADD9)
    - 1998 Obies--Winners (plus Ad Age Best) (Box ADD9)
    - 1998 Obies--Winners and finalists, 5 folders (Box ADD9)
    - 1999 Obies--0001 through 0567, 8 folders (Box ADD10)
    - 1999 Obies--0568 through 1118, 9 folders (Box ADD11)
    - 1999 Obies--Winners (Box ADD11)
    - 2000 Obies--0001 through 0492, 10 folders (Box ADD12)
    - 2000 Obies--0493 through 1026, 12 folders (Box ADD13)
    - Other finalists, 1999 (Box ADD13)
  - Presentations and curated slide collections, 1970-1997 and undated; 2
    - Brand Building (text and slides), 1997; 2 folders (Box ADD14)
    - The Competitive Edge, undated (Box ADD14)
    - Cosmetics, undated (Box ADD14)
    - Curated slides, undated; 2 folders (Box ADD14)
      Scope and Contents
      [Business, Media, Fashion, Beverages, OAAA, Consumer goods, International, Automotive, Entertainment, Travel, Public Service]
    - ESOA, undated (Box ADD14)
    - "Fleege" [Robert A. Fleege and Partners?], undated (Box ADD14)
    - Historical Outdoor Creative 1800-1970, 2 folders (Box ADD14)
    - Mixed Media Marriages II, undated (Box ADD14)
    - Outdoor Goes to College, undated (Box ADD14)
    - Retail, undated (Box ADD15)
    - Scenic outdoor slides, undated (Box ADD15)
    - Slides for Nancy Odenthal (OAAA Creative Library), undated (Box ADD15)
    - T4 Fashion; T5 Healthcare, undated (Box ADD15)
    - T6 Media, undated (Box ADD15)
    - T7 Restaurants; T8 Travel, undated (Box ADD15)
    - T9 International English; T10 Public Service; T11 International non-English, undated (Box ADD15)
    - Miscellaneous slides, mostly Eller, undated (Box ADD15)
    - Miscellaneous presentation slides, undated; 2 folders (Box ADD15)
  - Product categories, 1974-1996; 3
    - Apparel and accessories, 1983-1995 (Box ADD15)
    - Apparel and accessories, 1983-1995; 8 folders (Box ADD16)
    - Apparel and accessories--Apparel NEC-Berlei, 1985-1995; 2 folders (Box ADD16)
    - Apparel and accessories--Camp Beverly Hills-Gap, 1985-1993 (Box ADD17)
    - Automotive--Notebook 1: American, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box ADD17)
    - Automotive--Notebook 2: T110-T117, 1983-1995; 5 folders (Box ADD17)
    - Automotive--Notebook 3: T114-T131, 1977-1993; 2 folders (Box ADD17)
    - Automotive--Notebook 3: T114-T131, 1977-1993; 2 folders (Box ADD18)
    - Automotive--Notebook 4: T117-T151, 1985-1995; 5 folders (Box ADD18)
    - Automotive--Notebook 5: Acura to Dodge, 1977-1987; 2 folders (Box ADD18)
    - Automotive--Notebook 5: Dodge to Lexus, 1980-1993; 2 folders (Box ADD19)
    - Business/Finance--Notebook 1: B430-B450, 1985-1996; 5 folders (Box ADD19)
    - Business/Finance--Notebook 2: B120 (Financial products and services), 1985-1996; 3 folders (Box ADD19)
    - Business/Finance--Notebook 2: B120 (Financial products and services), 1985-1996; 2 folders (Box ADD20)
    - Communications, 1994-1995 (Box ADD20)
    - Drugs, toiletries and fitness, 1984-1994; 4 folders (Box ADD20)
    - Education: Schools, camps, seminars, 1986-1993 (Box ADD20)
    - Entertainment and amusement: Notebook 1: Motion pictures, 1989-1996; 3 folders (Box ADD21)
    - Entertainment and amusement: Notebook 2: Zoos, museums, participatory, sporting events, 1983-1996; 3 folders (Box ADD21)
    - Entertainment and amusement: Notebook 3: Zoos, museums, participatory, sporting events, 1986-1996; 3 folders (Box ADD21)
    - Entertainment and amusement: Notebook 3: Zoos, museums, participatory, sporting events, 1986-1996 (Box ADD22)
    - Entertainment and amusement: Notebook 4: Zoos, museums, participatory, sporting events, 1983-1993; 3 folders (Box ADD22)
    - Entertainment and amusement: Notebook 5: Zoos, museums, participatory, sporting events, 1983-1995; 3 folders (Box ADD22)
    - Fast Food, 1987-1996; 2 folders (Box ADD22)
    - Fast Food, 1987-1996; 3 folders (Box ADD23)
    - Food and beverages--Alcoholic, 1975-1993; 6 folders (Box ADD23)
    - Food and beverages--Notebook 1: Beer and ale, 1985-1993; 2 folders (Box ADD23)
    - Food and beverages--Notebook 1: Beer and ale, vodka, 1985-1993; 2 folders (Box ADD24)
    - Food and beverages--Notebook 2: Coffee, tea, fruit drinks, carbonated drinks, 1977-1993; 3 folders (Box ADD24)
    - Food and beverages--Notebook 3: Coffee, tea, fruit drinks, carbonated drinks, bottled water, 1986-1995; 4 folders (Box ADD24)
    - Food and beverages--Notebook 1: F600-F720, Beer and ale, whiskey, 1982-1994; 5 folders (Box ADD25)
    - Food and beverages--Notebook 2: F610, Beer and ale, alcoholic beverages, 1984-1995; 4 folders (Box ADD25)
    - Food and beverages--Notebook 2: F610, Beer and ale, alcoholic beverages, 1984-1995 (Box ADD26)
    - Food products--Notebook 1, 1984-1995; 5 folders (Box ADD26)
    - Food products--Notebook 2, 1983-1995; 4 folders (Box ADD26)
    - Food products--Notebook 2, 1983-1995 (Box ADD27)
    - Food products--Notebook 1: Candy, snacks, soft drinks, 1985-1993; 2 folders (Box ADD27)
    - Food products--Notebook 1: F120-F340, 1977-1992; 3 folders (Box ADD27)
    - General consumer goods--Sporting goods, ski equipment, pet supplies, 1976-1991; 2 folders (Box ADD27)
    - Healthcare, 1986-1995; 2 folders (Box ADD27)
    - Healthcare, 1986-1995; 2 folders (Box ADD28)
    - Media--Notebook 1: Television, cable, radio, 1979-1990; 5 folders (Box ADD28)
    - Media--Notebook 2: Television, cable, radio, 1989-1994; 3 folders (Box ADD28)
    - Media--Notebook 2: Television, cable, radio, 1989-1994; 2 folders (Box ADD29)
    - Media--Notebook 3: Print media (except books), radio, 1989-1994; 7 folders (Box ADD29)
    - Media--Notebook 4: Print media (except books), radio, television, 1984-1995 (Box ADD29)
    - Media--Notebook 4: Print media (except books), radio, television, 1984-1995; 5 folders (Box ADD30)
    - Restaurants--G300-G320, 1982-1995; 3 folders (Box ADD30)
    - Restaurants--G300-G320, 1979-1988; 2 folders (Box ADD30)
    - Restaurants--G300-G320, 1979-1988 (Box ADD31)
    - Retail stores--Notebook 1: Apparel, jewelry, department, 1979-1993; 3 folders (Box ADD31)
    - Retail stores--Notebook 2: Apparel and department, Robinson's, 1985-1986; 5 folderss (Box ADD31)
    - Retail stores: Department stores--Notebook 1: V410 apparel-department, 1986-1994 (Box ADD31)
    - Retail stores: Department stores--Notebook 1: V410 apparel-department, 1986-1994; 3 folders (Box ADD32)
    - Retail stores: Department stores--Notebook 1: miiscellaneous-department; V540 food and beverage, 1985-1994; 2 folders (Box ADD32)
    - Retail stores--Notebook 1: V410-V620: stores and shopping malls, 1982-1992; 4 folders (Box ADD32)
    - Retail stores--Notebook 1: V341-V620: stores and shopping malls, 1982-1992; 2 folders (Box ADD33)
    - Tobacco: cigarettes, tobacco and smoking accessories, 1985-1994; 4 folders (Box ADD33)
    - Transportation and travel--Notebook 1: Airlines, public transportation, 1974-1993; 4 folders (Box ADD33)
    - Transportation and travel--Notebook 1: Public transportation, resorts, travel accomodations, 1974-1993 (Box ADD34)
    - Transportation and travel--Notebook 2: Public transportation, resorts, travel accomodations, 1984-1994; 5 folders (Box ADD34)
    - Transportation and travel--Notebook 1: T420-T430; resorts, travel accomodations, 1982-1993; 3 folders (Box ADD34)
    - Transportation and travel--Notebook 1: T420-T430; resorts, travel accomodations, 1982-1993; 2 folders (Box ADD35)
    - Unsorted and duplicate slides, 1980-1995; 8 folders (Box ADD35)
    - Unsorted and duplicate slides, 1980-1995; 13 folders (Box ADD36)
    - Unsorted and duplicate slides, 1980-1995; 11 folders (Box ADD37)
    - Unsorted and duplicate slides, 1980-1995; 4 folders (Box ADD38)
  - Eller Media/Foster & Kleiser Slides, 1960-1986; 4
    - Automobiles, 1967-1986; 2 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Audi, 1971-1983 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Buick, 1970-1981; 2 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Cadillac, 1975 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Chevrolet, 1970-1983; 4 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Chrysler/Dodge/Plymouth, 1970-1984 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Datsun/Nissan, 1975-1984 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Ford, 1973-1986; 2 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Honda, 1974-1983; 2 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Jaguar, 1981-1984 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Lincoln-Mercury, 1980-1983 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Mazda, 1971-1983 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Peugeot, Renault, 1972-1978 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Pontiac, 1976-1977 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Subaru, Suzuki, 1979-1985 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Toyota, 1970-1985 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Volkswagen, 1971-1984; 3 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Dealerships, 1968-1984; 3 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Oil and Gas, 1965-1974 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Oil and Gas--Chevron/Standard, 1962-1969 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Oil and Gas--Douglas, 1966-1967 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Oil and Gas--Enco/Exxon, 1967-1972 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Oil and Gas--Gulf, 1967-1972 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Oil and Gas--Texaco, 1967-1970 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Oil and Gas--Union 76, 1963-1969 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Parts and Supplies, 1977-1986 (Box ADD39)
    - Automobiles--Trucks and Motorcycles, 1979-1984 (Box ADD39)
    - Banks and Savings & Loan, 1967-1982; 2 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Banks and Savings & Loan--Union Bank, 1961-1977 (Box ADD39)
    - Banks and Savings & Loan--Wells Fargo, 1965-1971 (Box ADD39)
    - Beverages, 1972-1979 (Box ADD39)
    - Beverages--Beer, 1977-1982 (Box ADD39)
    - Beverages--Coffee, 1966-1977 (Box ADD39)
    - Building Supplies/Contractors, 1965-1984 (Box ADD39)
    - Building Supplies/Contractors--Lakewood Pipe, 1972 (Box ADD39)
    - Cigarettes, 1971-1982 (Box ADD39)
    - Cigarettes--L&M, 1974-1975 (Box ADD39)
    - Cigarettes--Marlboro, 1972-1977 (Box ADD39)
    - Cigarettes--Salem/Camel/Real, 1971-1980; 2 folders (Box ADD39)
    - Cigarettes--Winston, 1972-1976 (Box ADD39)
    - Department Stores, Shopping Centers, 1964-1986 (Box ADD39)
    - Department Stores, Shopping Centers--Anell's, 1966-1971 (Box ADD39)
    - Department Stores, Shopping Centers--Inland Center, 1969 (Box ADD39)
    - Department Stores, Shopping Centers--Mission Valley, 1963-1969 (Box ADD39)
    - Department Stores, Shopping Centers--Montgomery Ward, 1970-1977 (Box ADD39)
    - Department Stores, Shopping Centers--Ohrbach's, 1961-1968 (Box ADD39)
    - Department Stores, Shopping Centers--Topanga Plaza, 1966-1968 (Box ADD39)
    - Electronics/Televisions, 1964-1978 (Box ADD39)
    - Foods, 1981-1984 (Box ADD39)
    - Household Goods, 1963-1986 (Box ADD39)
    - Household Goods--Payne, 1972 (Box ADD39)
    - Insurance, 1981-1985 (Box ADD39)
    - Kitchen and Laundry, 1963-1976 (Box ADD39)
    - Lawn and Garden/Agriculture, 1972-1982 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor, 1969-1978 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Scotch, 1965-1975 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Scotch--White Horse, 1968-1974 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Tequila/Mexcal, 1974-1982 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Tequila/Mexcal--Arandas, Jose Cuervo, Olmeca, 1973-1979 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Tequila/Mexcal--Puerto Vallarta, 1969-1981 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Tequila/Mexcal--Valido Fresa, 1975 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Vodka, 1969-1981 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Vodka--Kamchatka, 1971-1975 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Vodka--Smirnoff, 1968-1983 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Vodka--Stolichnaya, 1975-1982 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Vodka--Wolfschmidt, 1967-1980 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Whiskey (U.S. and Canadian), 1969-1980 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Whiskey (U.S. and Canadian)--Canadian Club, 1976-1978 (Box ADD39)
    - Liquor--Whiskey (U.S. and Canadian)--Seagrams, 1964-1976 (Box ADD39)
    - Media--Print, 1978-1983 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio, 1960-1984; 2 folders (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--KABC, 1969-1975 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--KBIG, 1975-1979 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--KFI, 1963-1979 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--KLAC, 1969-1970 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--KMPC, 1967-1980 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--KNX, 1968-1981 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--KPOL, 1969-1977 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--KSON, 1969-1979 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Radio--XTRA, 1966-1978 (Box ADD40)
    - Media--Television, 1978-1984 (Box ADD40)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1978 (Box ADD40)
    - Mortuaries, 1962-1984 (Box ADD40)
    - Mortuaries--Inglewood, 1964-1981 (Box ADD40)
    - Mortuaries--Rose Hills, 1967-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service, 1971-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service--Crime and Safety, 1977-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service--Education, 1971-1981 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service--Environment/Conservation, 1967-1981; 2 folders (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service--Eyes and Ears Foundation, 1977 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service--Health and Medical, 1973-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service--Municipal, 1972-0982 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service--Religion, 1973-1981 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Service--Youth, 1971-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Utility--Electric, 1966-1978 (Box ADD40)
    - Public Utility--Gas, 1964-1979 (Box ADD40)
    - Real Estate, 1967-1979 (Box ADD40)
    - Restaurants, 1971-1983; 2 folders (Box ADD40)
    - Restaurants--Jack-in-the-Box, 1973-1977 (Box ADD40)
    - Restaurants--McDonald's, 1971-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Restaurants--Winchell's, 1981-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Retail, 1973-1986 (Box ADD40)
    - Telephone Service--General Telephone (GTE), 1967-1974 (Box ADD40)
    - Telephone Service--Pacific Telephone (PacTel), 1964-1974 (Box ADD40)
    - Telephone Service--Yellow Pages, 1977-1981 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel, 1971-1979 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines, 1969-1983 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--Air California, 1969-1981 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--Air Canada, 1969-1971 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--Alaska Airlines, 1981 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--American, 1967-1982; 2 folders (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--BOAC/British Air, 1967-1980 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--Continental, 1977-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--National, 1970-1976 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--Republic/Hughes, 1971-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Airlines--Western, 1967-1981 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Bus, 1973 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--California, 1972-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Cruise Lines, 1968-1976 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Entertainment, 1964-1983; 3 folders (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Hotels, 1977-1983 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Las Vegas, 1972-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Nevada, 1976-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Palm Springs (Calif.), 1976-1982 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Railroads, 1969-1976 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Railroads--Amtrak, 1973 (Box ADD40)
    - Travel--Utah, 1979-1982 (Box ADD40)